pandia.com 2003-12-03

# Pandia, privacy policy

### Email addresses

Pandia will never give your email address to any other company or organisation, nor will we ever use it to send you "junk" or "spam" email. If you subscribe to a newsletter or news service, a newsletter is what you get. Period.

P&S Koch has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: the Pandia Search Central. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. 

Our site's registration forms may require users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We may use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about Pandia. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings. 

Demographic and profile data may also be collected at our site. We may use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information may be shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. But we will not under any circumstance give the visitors' e-mail address, name or address to advertisers. 

This site contains links to other sites. Pandia is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

The Pandia Bookstore is operated in association with Amazon.com. Please see [Amazon.com's privacy statement](http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/subst/misc/policy/privacy.html/ref=gw_m_ln_nh_pp/002-8865118-7457809) for more information. 

We may use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. Ads may contain cookies, and appear to be coming from our site, but in reality they are coming from our partners who are serving ads on our site. 

With the exception of Pandia Radio Search our site does not use cookies. We do not have access to any information about you from cookies you might receive while visiting our site.

The Pandia Radio Search, which is operated by the TVRadio Network, may use a cookie to keep track of the radio stations you have marked as "favourites". This cookie cannot be traced to you personally, and will not be used to gather information about you. 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

## Children's Guidelines

Pandia will NOT collect online contact information from children without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent. 

Pandia will NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent. 

Pandia will NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent. 

Pandia will NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent. 

Pandia will NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity. 

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site will provide users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can write to [pandia@pandia.com](mailto:susannek@powertech.no).
